{
  "name": "Roman Numerals",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Write the Roman numeral for the following number:\n36",
      "answers": ["XXXVI"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the Roman numeral for the following number:\n45",
      "answers": ["XLV"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the Roman numeral for the following number:\n359",
      "answers": ["CCCLIX"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the Roman numeral for the following number:\n198",
      "answers": ["CXCVIII"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the Roman numeral for the following number:\n88",
      "answers": ["LXXXVIII"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the Roman numeral for the following number:\n112",
      "answers": ["CXII"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the Hindu-Arabic numeral for the following Roman numeral:\nXIX",
      "answers": ["19"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the Hindu-Arabic numeral for the following Roman numeral:\nXLIV",
      "answers": ["44"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the Hindu-Arabic numeral for the following Roman numeral:\nXCV",
      "answers": ["95"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the Hindu-Arabic numeral for the following Roman numeral:\nCMXXXVIII",
      "answers": ["938"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the Hindu-Arabic numeral for the following Roman numeral:\nLVII",
      "answers": ["57"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the Hindu-Arabic numeral for the following Roman numeral:\nCDV",
      "answers": ["405"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the Hindu-Arabic numeral for the following Roman numeral:\nCMXVI",
      "answers": ["916"],
      "keyboard": "digits_only",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the sum of the following and write answer in Roman numeral:\nXXX + XXIV",
      "answers": ["LIV"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the sum of the following and write answer in Roman numeral:\nXIX + L",
      "answers": ["LXIX"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the sum of the following and write answer in Roman numeral:\nXII + VIII + XXII",
      "answers": ["XLII"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the sum of the following and write answer in Roman numeral:\nXXXIV + L",
      "answers": ["LXXXIV"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the difference of the following and write answer in Roman numeral:\n40 - 20",
      "answers": ["XX"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the difference of the following and write answer in Roman numeral:\n50 - 21",
      "answers": ["XXIX"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the difference of the following and write answer in Roman numeral:\n50 - 19",
      "answers": ["XXXI"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the difference of the following and write answer in Roman numeral:\n60 - 40",
      "answers": ["XX"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank with Roman numeral:\nNovember has ______ days.",
      "answers": ["XXX"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank with Roman numeral:\nFebruary has XXVIII or _____ days.",
      "answers": ["XXIX"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank with Roman numeral:\nA person has _____ teeth.",
      "answers": ["XXXII"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    },
    {
      "question": "Fill in the blank with Roman numeral:\nA year has _____ weeks.",
      "answers": ["LII"],
      "keyboard": "roman_numeral",
      "timeout": 180
    }
  ]
}